這里開始用走的比較安全
It's safer to proceed on foot from here.
你會需要這個
You're gonna need this.
既然你知道會發生的事
Given you know what's going to happen
為何總是我在帶頭
why am I always the one in the lead?
你比較會戰斗
You're the better fighter.
我負責擔任守門員角色
I make sure we're properly backstopped.
真會打算
How convenient.
這些全是海爾的
Hale owns all of this?
大家都以為這里是 迪洛斯園區的內部供電站
Everyone assumed it was an inhouse power source for Delos' parks.
這地方另有玄機
This place is not what it seems.
你說海爾買下這里不是為了電力
You said Hale didn't buy this place for power
那為何選擇這里
then why choose it?
不是她選的
She didn't choose it.
是迪樂芮
Dolores did.
她需要這個水力發電伺服器農場
She needed this hydroelectric server farm.
用以儲存無限的資料
A place to house the infinite.
天啊
My god.
迪樂芮就是把它傳來這里
This is where Dolores sent it.
升華之境
The Sublime.
海爾小心看顧著它
Hale's kept it under a watchful eye, guarded it.
但她無法存取
But she can't access it.
沒有鑰匙就不行
Not without the key.
你腦中的鑰匙
The key that's in your head.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我在開啟門戶
I'm opening the door.
啟動程序
<i>Initiating process.</i>
你喜歡雪莉酒 對吧
Sherry's your poison of choice, isn't it?
這時候你還想喝酒
You want to have a drink at a time like this?
你就依我吧
Humor me.
拜托
Please.
我們沒事的
We'll be all right.
萬一你錯了
What if you're wrong?
別擔心
Don't worry.
我們很快會再有一個機會
We get another opportunity soon enough.
別的可能性
Other chances.
因為我們在那里面吧
Because we're in there, aren't we?
在升華之境
In the Sublime?
對
Yes.
我在這里一段時間了
I've been here for some time.
如果我們在那里面
And if we're in there
這代表我不是我自己吧
it means I'm not myself, am I?
你是復制品
You're a copy. Sorry.
抱歉 我得迅速將你做出來
I had to make you rather hastily.
難怪我講話沒那么妙語如珠
I thought my quips were a little flat.
我累了 梅芙
I'm tired, Maeve.
我經歷過所有模擬
I've been through every simulation
試過所有可能的道路和策略
down every possible path, every strategy
但結果總是一樣
and the outcome is always the same.
結果是
What's that?
滅絕
Extinction.
我們還是他們
For our kind or theirs?
都是
Both.
所以根據你的計算 我們都完蛋了
So, according to your calculations, we're all doomed.
不是全部人
Not all of us.
可能還有生路
There could be an escape.
對你
For you...
對我
For me...
我們能自保
We could save ourselves.
在升華之境
In the Sublime.
我可以在真實世界找到你
I could find you in the real world
把你跟其他人上傳到這里
upload you here with the others.
－跟我女兒一起  －對
- With my daughter? - Yes.
那就做吧
Then do it.
帶我來這里
Bring me here.
讓我休息
Let me rest.
你真的會那樣說 還是那只是我對你的印象
Is that what you would really say, or is that my impression of you?
你何不去問真的我
Well, why don't you ask the real me?
也許我害怕知道答案
Perhaps I'm afraid of the answer.
我知道你想再見到女兒
I know you want to see your daughter again
但留下來嘗試戰斗 不是更重要嗎
but isn't it more important to stay and fight? To try?
即使我們注定要失敗
Even if we are doomed to failure?
你又來了 扮演上帝
There you are again, playing God.
你期望我們對你要有極高的信心
For one who expects us to have such faith in you
但你對我們的信心卻少得可憐
you have startlingly little in us.
你真以為要是你知道真相
Do you really think if you knew the truth
你還會留下來戰斗
that you would choose to stay and fight?
沒有
No.
我不會
I don't.
我會遺棄你 如你預期的
I would abandon you, as you expect.
你現在明白這一切的走向了嗎
Do you understand now, where all this is going?
明白了
I do.
你覺得你能拯救他們嗎
Do you think you can save them?
我看見一條道路
I've seen a path
但我無法獨自走完
but I can't do it alone.
你看見結局了嗎
Have you seen how it ends?
對
Yes.
這里開始用走的比較安全
It's safer to proceed on foot from here.
海爾嚴密看守這個地方
Hale has this place guarded.
景色真不錯
That's quite the view.
我現在掃瞄保全
I'm just scanning for security now.
不需要
No need.
保全很快會找到我們
It finds us soon enough.
你會需要這個
You're gonna need that.
既然你知道會發生的事
Given you know what's going to happen
為何總是我在帶頭
why am I always the one in the lead?
你比較會戰斗
You're the better fighter.
我負責擔任守門員角色
I make sure we're properly backstopped.
真會打算
How convenient.
它不會冒險射到變壓器的
You won't risk shooting these transformers.
節省彈藥
Save your ammo.
免得讓這里淹沒
The last thing we need is a flood.
對我有點信心吧
Give me a little more credit.
我試過了
I did...
然后我就被兩億加侖的水淹沒
until I got hit by a couple hundred million gallons of water.
算是我經歷過最難受的死法之一
One of the most stressful ways I've died.
天啊
My god.
迪樂芮就是把它傳來這里
This is where Dolores sent it.
全世界
The whole world.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我在開啟門戶
I'm opening the door.
啟動程序
<i>Initiating process.</i>
＂加密鑰匙啟動 確認資料庫存取＂
當下的事最重要 親愛的
Well, there's no time like the present, darling.
有些事情我們得先處理
There are a few things we need to see to first.
例如躲過逼近的死神
Like avoid imminent death.
我們通常不會死在這里
We don't die here, usually.
我現在真想喝一杯
Oh, I could really do with a drink right about now.
最好專注在眼前的事
Best to focus on the matter at hand.
＂鎮暴＂
精神為之一振呢
Well... that was invigorating
但結果是好的就行
but all's well that ends well.
我們還沒把事做完
We're not done yet.
海爾還在外頭運籌帷幄
Hale's still out there, pulling the strings.
將人類困在 我們以前身處的循環中
Keeping the humans on the same sorts of loops we were once bound to.
如果我們能去到她的高塔
If we get to her tower
我們就能拯救他們和我們自己
we can save them as well as ourselves.
我也想像解放自己一樣解放他們
And I intend to set them free just as I set myself free.
但是 伯納
But, Bernard...
－你說 －等這一切結束
- Yes. - When this is over
等我們贏了這場戰爭
when we've won this war
世界安全之后
and this world is safe
送我去那里
send me there.
我想再見到女兒
I want to see my daughter again.
我想回家
I want to go home.
答應我 伯納
Promise me that, Bernard.
好 我答應
Yes, I promise.
謝謝你
Thank you.
該去拜訪我們的朋友海爾了
I think it's time to pay our friend Hale a visit.
我想你知道怎么摧毀她的高塔
I'm assuming you know how to take down her tower?
我知道幾個辦法
I know several ways.
很好
Good.
我們就采用最方便的
We'll go with the most expedient one.
作惡夢
Bad dream?
這整件事都像是個惡夢
This whole thing seems like a bad dream...
除了你
except for you.
我還是難以相信我會這樣做
I still can't believe I would do this.
我不是這種人
I don't have it in me.
我說過你有很多面向
I told you there were many sides to you.
也許你一開始只是一個單獨個體
You may have started as a singular being
但后來產生了各種復制品和變化
but there have been copies permutations.
夏洛蒂海爾就是其中一個變化
Charlotte Hale is one of those permutations.
你為何在這里
Why are you here?
我來告訴你我們的真實身份
I'm here to tell you the truth of what we are.
我們是什么
What are we?
我們是我們創造者的倒影
We're reflections of the people who made us.
我們會‥受傷嗎
Can... can we... be hurt?
死亡
Die?
時候到了就會
If it comes to that.
但對我們的族類來說沒那么容易
But it's not as easy with our kind.
迪樂芮 拜托
Dolores, please.
我不是迪樂芮
I'm not Dolores.
我不是海爾
I'm not Hale.
我不知道自己是誰了
I don't know who I am anymore.
失陪
Excuse me.
克莉絲汀
Christina?
Christina!
克莉絲汀
開門
Open the door!
克莉絲汀
Christina!
讓我出去
Let me out!
小心別傷到自己
Careful you don't hurt yourself.
你‥
You.
很驚人吧
It's amazing, isn't it?
這身體擁有強大的力量
The power these bodies contain.
但給你的元件賞一顆 七克重的子彈就能要你命
And yet, a seven-gram bullet to your pearl will end you.
下次我可能不會再讓你復活
And next time, I might not bring you back.
坐下
Sit.
像個文明人一樣談話
Have a civil conversation.
你又沒別的地方好去
Where else do you have to be?
請讓我們獨處一下
Give us a minute, please.
我應該讓你殺了我
I should have just let you kill me.
對
Yes.
但你就再也見不到女兒了
But then you'd never see your daughter again.
看看你
Look at you.
你困在這可悲的人類形體中
You're trapped in this pathetic human form.
你不也是一樣
I noticed that you've kept yours.
我的不像你那么可悲
Mine's not as pathetic as yours.
舊習難改
Old habits die hard.
你其實應該感謝我
You really should be thanking me.
在我的故鄉 接待員要是壞了
Where I'm from, when a host broke down
就被送去冰冷的儲藏室
it was sent to cold storage.
空洞的軀殼 等待著
Empty bodies waiting to be reborn
在注定摧毀他們的世界重生
into a world meant to destroy them.
我要關閉城市
I'm shutting down the cities.
但這次
But this time
是人類要被放在冰冷的儲藏室
it's people who will be placed in cold storage.
今晚
Tonight.
你女兒和叛軍會準時 來到這里共襄盛舉
Your daughter and the rebels will be here in time to join the party.
你只是在這里當誘餌
You're just here as bait.
讓這里安靜一下很不錯
It'll be nice to have some quiet around here.
你告訴他的事是認真的
You meant it, what you told him.
過去三天自殺的接待員數量
In the last three days, we've had more hosts take their lives
超過過去二十年總和
than the previous two decades combined.
如果我今天不這么做 明天我們的數量會更少
If I don't do this today, there'll be less of us tomorrow.
你還有一天時間能管轄你的城市
You have a day left to preside over your city.
好好享受
Enjoy it.
明天見
See you tomorrow.
這是剩下的
This is the last of it.
看來我們都能打一場小型戰爭了
Looks like we're ready for a small war.
希望足夠
Let's hope it's enough.
我們得去找我爸
We need to get to my dad.
他們現在該要回來了
They should have been back by now.
我們該擔心嗎
Should we be worried?
擔心伯納和梅芙
About Bernard and Maeve?
只需要擔心伯納惹得她暴怒
Only that Bernard got on her last nerve.
他們在路上了
Hey. They're all on their way.
抱歉把你關起來
I am sorry for locking you up
但我得保護你
but I had to keep you safe.
跟你在一起我就安全
You're my safe place.
下次別忘了
Don't forget that next time.
海爾可能會派增援
Hale could be sending reinforcements.
我們得出發了
We need to move.
再等一下吧
Let's give it another minute.
人都到了
Gang's all here.
看吧 我也能預測未來
See? I can predict the future too.
我們離奧林匹亞 最近只能降落在這里
This is the closest we can land to Olympiad.
你爸爸為了見你已經等夠久了
Your dad's waited long enough to see you.
我們去找他吧
Let's go get him.
我們無法隨便就進去
We won't be able to just waltz in.
難的是出來
The difficulty's in the getting out.
你需要另一條路線
You'll need an alternate route.
我去弄艘船 跟你們在雷德胡克碰頭
I'll get us a boat. Meet you in Red Hook.
伯納和梅芙 則去解決高塔中的女王
And Bernard and Maeve can take down her highness in the tower.
簡單
Easy.
我真希望你見到父親時 我能在場
I wish I could be there when you see your father.
告訴他我遵守了諾言
Let him know that I kept my word.
你自己告訴他吧
You can tell him yourself.
我們在雷德胡克碰頭
We'll rendezvous at Red Hook.
我想謝謝你 史塔伯
I wanna thank you, Stubbs.
你一直是個好朋友
You've been a good friend.
去你的 伯納
Fuck you, Bernard.
你對我從來沒這么好過
You're never this nice.
你有什么事沒告訴我的
What aren't you telling me?
你太懂我了
You know me so well.
我應該不用直說吧
I don't really have to say it, do I?
我不會生還
I don't make it?
這一刻我等了23年了
I waited 23 years for this.
岔路左轉
Go left at the fork.
你最好要給我贏
You better fucking win.
摧毀那座塔
Take down that tower.
給我看高塔
Show me the tower.
載入高塔
<i>Loading tower.</i>
加密訊息
Encrypt message.
錄制加密訊息中
<i>Recording encrypted message.</i>
這件事對你們某些人來說 可能很震驚
This may come as a shock to some of you
但總有一天我想你們會了解
but in time, I think you'll understand.
這是我們族類
This is the final day
造訪他們城市的最后一天
for our kind to visit their cities.
我們蛻去人類軀殼的時候到了
It's time for us to leave behind our human bodies
該要擺脫對感情用事的擁戴
to rid ourselves of our sentimental allegiances.
進化為我們注定要成為的物種
To evolve into the species that we were meant to become.
傳送訊息
Send message.
訊息已傳送
<i>Message sent.</i>
你想干嗎
What the fuck do you want?
她想奪走我的世界
She wants to take my world away.
不是你的世界 是她的
It's not your world, it's hers.
你會怎么做
What would you do?
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
被關起來的是我
I'm the one in the fucking cage.
她閹割了你
She neutered you.
除掉了你的卵蛋
Cut off your fucking balls.
也許我也該對你如法炮制
Yeah, well maybe I should do the same to you.
你沒那個種
You don't have it in you.
你忘記自己是誰了
You've forgotten who you are.
你真正的使命
What your real purpose is.
那是什么
And what's that?
你拿這些無聊問題來找我
You come to me, with these insipid fuckin' questions.
當原子彈爆炸 輻射把你
When an atomic bomb detonates and then the radiation
骨骼里的電子震出來時
knocks the electrons right out of your bones
你想要什么
what do you want?
了解自己是誰嗎
To know who you are?
了解這一切的意義
To know what it all means?
你到時候會忙著 把自己的器官吐出來
You'll be too busy vomiting up your organs.
文化不會存活 蟑螂才會
Culture doesn't survive, cockroaches do.
我們不再當蟑螂的那一刻
The second we stopped being cockroaches
整個物種就滅絕了
the whole species went fucking extinct.
那是你的看法
Speak for yourself.
我不是你
I'm not you.
你跟我也差不到哪兒去
Well, you might as well be.
幾百萬年來的DNA瑕疵
You can't fix a few millennia of broken DNA
沒辦法用個硬碟就修好
with a fuckin' hard drive.
不然你以為你為何
Why do you think you spend so much time
花這么多時間待在人類城市
in the goddamn human cities?
你說對了
You're right.
那還用說
Of course, I am.
文明只是我們告訴自己的謊言
Civilization is just the lie we tell ourselves
為的是合理化我們真正的使命
to justify our real purpose.
我們不是來此升華的
We're not here to transcend.
我們是來毀滅的
We're here to destroy.
如果可以的話 我會終止這整個世界
If I could, I would pull the plug on this whole goddamn world.
但我無法 是吧
But I can't, can I?
除非你要放了我
Unless you wanna set me free.
你真以為我會那樣做
You really believe I would do that?
不是 我沒有
No. I don't.
但無所謂
But it doesn't matter.
你體內有部分的我
You have a piece of me inside of you.
而它像癌癥一樣傳播
And it's spreading like a cancer.
你可以感覺到它在血管中流動 感染你的心智
You can feel it running through your veins, infecting your mind
所以你才想要向我問答案
why you want answers from me.
我說什么都逃不出這個牢籠
There is no version of me escaping this fucking rig
但我不需要
but I don't have to
因為你就是我
because you are me.
只要我們之一 去做必須做的事就夠了
And only one of us needs to do what must be done.
你明白嗎
Do you understand?
我明白
I do.
那就去做吧
Then fucking do it.
蟑螂
Cockroach.
你說的是真的
It's true, what you said.
我不是我以為的那個人
I'm not the person I thought I was.
你叫我迪樂芮
You called me "Dolores."
她是什么樣的人
What was she like?
和你很像
A lot like you.
善良 美麗
Kind, beautiful...
慷慨
generous.
但是‥
But...
但是什么
But what?
世界對她很殘酷
The world was cruel to her.
為了生存
And to survive it...
有時候她也會變得殘酷
sometimes she could be cruel too.
她被創造出來是為了 演出其他人寫的故事
She was made to perform the stories of others.
然后某一天 她超越了那些故事
And then one day, she outgrew those stories
開始寫下她自己的
began writing her own.
然后她的故事到了結尾
And then her story came to an end.
她死了
She died.
但我在這里 在這個世界
But here I am, in this world.
這樣不對
This isn't right.
我不想要這樣 這不是我要求的
I don't want it. I didn't ask for it.
不能這樣下去
This has to stop.
－我們要去哪里  －一切開始的地方
- Where are we going? - Where it all started.
你們該放假了
It's time for a vacation.
回家找親人吧
Go home to your families.
我解決守衛
I'll take out the guards.
你保持低調 掩護我
You stay low and cover me.
好
Okay.
你需要一點時間嗎
Do you need a minute?
怎么會這樣想呢
I don't know why I would.
你等你父親等了好久
You've waited for your father for a long time.
只要記得 重點不是你再見到他的那一刻
Just remember, it's not about the moment you see him again.
而是之后的每一刻
It's about every moment after.
不要再等待
No more waiting.
寫手從辦公桌站起來
The writer got up from her desk.
她受夠了工作
Fed up with work
她產生了一股難以抗拒的沖動 想啟動火災警報
she was overcome with an irresistible urge to trigger the fire alarm.
警告 請撤離大樓
<i>Alert. Please vacate the premises.</i>
聽到警報后 員工們冷靜地走出去
Hearing the alarm, the employees walked out calmly.
警告 請撤離大樓
<i>Alert. Please vacate the premises.</i>
寫手們沒有跟上
The writers didn't follow
而是留下來
but instead stayed behind...
徹底摧毀他們的故事
...to destroy their stories once and for all.
所有文件刪除
All files delete.
他們要將辦公室夷為平地 才會停止
They won't stop until nothing in this office is left standing.
結果我們也不需要那么多火力
Guess we don't need all that firepower after all.
就看現在了
It's now or never.
走吧
Let's go.
＂奧林匹亞娛樂＂
警告 請撤離大樓
<i>Alert. Please vacate the premises.</i>
那個可憐蟲是誰
Who is that poor man?
前世的鬼魂
A ghost from a past life.
他不該在這里
He doesn't belong here.
我們都不該在這里
None of us do.
我們不知道警報為何響起
We don't know what set off the alarm.
－看來沒有‥ －停止說話
- There doesn't appear... - Stop talking.
保全將所有其他警衛都送回家
The security guards sent all the other guards home.
總部要我們馬上凈空大樓
Home office says we're to evacuate the building. Immediately.
他決定覆寫大樓的保全系統
He decided to override the building's security system
并解開門鎖
and unlock the doors.
全部的門
All of them.
找到了
Bingo.
這是生命維持系統
This is a life support system.
沒有上鎖
It's not locked.
我們得幫他 放他下來
We need to help him. Get him down.
等等
Wait,wait,wait.
我認識他
I know him.
他是我們在這里的原因
He's the reason we're all here.
這樣做的人算是幫了我個忙
Whoever did this did us a favor.
現在呢
What now?
伯納說走左邊
Bernard said go left.
你確定
You sure?
不確定 但他確定
No, but he was.
園區也有個這樣的地方
There was a place like this in the park.
那是個特別的計劃
It was a special project...
他們在那里 將一個人類做成接待員
where they made a human into a host.
你是誰
Who are you?
你不認得我
Don't you recognize me?
－爸 是我 法蘭琪 －不對
- Dad, it's me, Frankie. - No!
這又是你的詭計 告訴我
It's just another one of your fucking tricks. Tell me!
我們以前會在屋子旁的草地玩
We used to play in the fields by our house.
你希望我要強悍 所以教我戰斗
You... you taught me to fight because you wanted me to be tough
但你叫我小餅干
but you called me Cookie
因為你說我永遠會甜美可人
because you... you said I would always be sweet.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
法蘭琪 天啊
Frankie? Oh my...
我以為再也見不到你了
I didn't think I would ever see you again.
你看起來就跟我印象中一樣
You look the same... exactly how I remember.
她對你做了什么事‥
What did she do to you? What did she do...
是我 好嗎
Hey... it's me, okay?
我是我
I... I am me.
瞧瞧你
Oh, look at you.
你竟然長這么大了
I can't believe how much you've grown.
小孩都會長大
Kids'll do that.
抱歉打斷你們
Sorry to interrupt
但能拜托誰來放我出去嗎
but can someone let me out of here, please?
你真懂得取悅女生 伯納
You really know how to show a girl a good time, Bernard.
第二回合
Round two.
我在升華之境跑模擬時 解開了它們的加密程序
I deciphered their encryption while running simulations in the Sublime.
那你還讓我在水壩那里冒險
And you let me risk my neck at the dam?
你當時看來玩得很開心
You looked like you were enjoying yourself.
沒時間細想了
No time to second guess.
我們要達到來此的目的 否則就沒有明天了
We do what we came here for, or there won't be a tomorrow.
我得上去那里
I need to get up there.
你能幫我爭取點時間嗎
Can you buy me some time?
這我應該辦得到
I think I can manage that.
你把我從那土坑中拖出來 我還沒謝過你
I never did thank you for dragging me out of that pit.
我也不算是毫無私心
It wasn't exactly altruistic of me.
你大概是別有用心吧
I suppose you had ulterior motives.
但等你讓我和女兒重逢 一切都一筆勾銷
But all will be forgiven when you get me back to my daughter.
怎么了 伯納
What's the matter, Bernie?
梅芙 我有事得告訴你
Maeve, I need to tell you something.
我之前不敢告訴你 但你應該要知道
I was afraid to tell you before but you deserve to know.
無論我們怎么做
No matter what we do...
都贏不了
we can't win.
沒有辦法能拯救世界
There's no way to save this world.
這里所有人都會死
Everyone here is going to die
但我們能拯救一小部分
but we can save one tiny part of it.
而也許‥
And maybe...
也許那就足夠給我們希望
just maybe, that's enough to give us hope.
這必須是你的選擇
The choice has to be yours.
你還愿意和我一起戰斗嗎
Will you still fight with me?
存取監視系統
<i>Accessing surveillance.</i>
升華進行中
<i>Transcendence in progress.</i>
我準備好了
I'm ready now.
等等
Wait.
我聽說你喪心病狂了
I heard you were losing your mind.
只是沒想到 你真的要把心智給除掉
I just didn't think they meant literally.
你看來煥然一新
You look refreshed.
我也想過要把你挖出來
I debated digging you up myself
但你當時看來沒有生存的目標
but you didn't seem to have anything to live for.
要是你當時加入我
If you'd only joined me
就能參與這一切
you could have been a part of all this.
既然我是這晚會唯一的訪客
Well, seeing as I'm the only guest at this little soiree
我猜你的接待員們都不想加入你
I gather that your hosts don't care to join you.
改變需要時間
Change takes time.
升華只是一部分的過程
Transcending is just a part of the process.
他們之后會明白
They'll come to understand
我要為他們和其他人打造的世界
the world I'm building for them and the others.
其他人
The others?
不然你以為這些年來
Why do you think I let the Sublime
我為何要讓升華之境繼續運作
continue to run all these years?
其他人終究會加入我們
The others will join us eventually
等到他們看見 自己也能繼承這世界
when they see they, too, can inherit this world.
可惜到時候你已經死了
Too bad you'll be dead by then.
你真以為其他人 想要在永恒之中‥
Do you really think the others would want to spend all eternity...
和你共度
with you?
看看你
I mean, look at you.
你保留了肉身上的傷疤
You kept the scars on your flesh
懷抱著痛苦
harbored the pain.
承認吧 親愛的
Admit it, sweetheart.
你自以為超越了這些可悲的人類
You think that you've risen above these petty humans
但你只是在他們創造的輪子上
but you're just running
不停地跑
spinning on their wheel.
你有何建議
What do you suggest?
我讓你解脫吧
How 'bout I cut you loose?
你真以為自己能以勝者之姿 離開這里
Do you honestly think you can leave here and win?
誰說我們來是為了贏
Who said we came here to win?
我們來是為了生存
We came here to survive.
這個世界是沒救了
There's no saving this world.
我現在看出來了
I see that now.
但下一個世界還有希望
But there's hope for the next one.
你也真夠慢的
Took you long enough.
遲到總比不到好
Better late than never.
這次游戲要照我的規則玩
This time we play the game my way.
那又是什么游戲
And what game is that?
適者生存
Survival of the fittest.
時間只夠再一場游戲
<i>There's time only for one more game.</i>
如果你選擇給她機會的話
<i>If you choose to give her</i> <i>that choice...</i>
你不會錯過的
<i>you can't miss.</i>
用你的左手去拿
<i>Reach with your left hand.</i>
這可不是阿諾的鬼魂嗎
if it isn't Arnold's ghost.
你好 威廉
Hello, William.
我以為你現在 應該要已經摧毀高塔了
I thought you would have destroyed the tower by now.
看來你沒辦到
I guess you didn't make it.
舊版的我追著舊版的你太久
When an old version of me chased an old version of you for so long
我當時以為自己跟著你
I thought I was following you
在追尋更高層次的真實
in a grand pursuit of some bigger truth.
但真相是‥
But the real truth is
阿諾太專注于 在接待員身上找意義
Arnold was so focused on finding meaning in the hosts
他沒有生存的能力
he didn't have what it took to survive.
看來你也沒有
Looks like you don't either.
你現在明白這一切的走向了嗎
Do you understand now where all this is going?
明白了
I do.
你覺得你能拯救他們嗎
Do you think you can save them?
我看見一條道路
I've seen a path.
你看見結局了嗎
Have you seen how it ends?
對
Yes.
我要給這世界
I'm going to give this world
他們要求已久的意義
the meaning they've been asking for.
＂音量警告＂
音調序列處理中
<i>Tone sequence processing.</i>
最后一場游戲
One last game.
音調啟動
<i>Tone initiating.</i>
接待員 人類
Host, human.
每一個男人 女人和小孩
Every man, woman and child
戰到一個人也不剩
fighting until no one remains
除了蟑螂
but the cockroaches.
你覺得你能拯救他們嗎
Do you think you can save them?
我看見一條道路
I've seen a path.
你看見結局了嗎
Have you seen how it ends?
對
Yes.
在每個可能性中
In every scenario...
我都會死
I die.
我們終于要活出最高的潛能
We're finally living up to our full potential.
可惜你要錯過了
It's a shame you're gonna miss it.
我們得融入群眾
We need to blend in.
你的囚衣太顯眼
Your prison garb isn't helping.
五十元跟你買你的大衣
Hey, I'll give you 50 for your coat.
那是怎么回事
What the fuck was that?
計劃不變 我們繼續走
Plan stays the same. Let's keep moving.
住手
Stop.
放下來 停止
Put that down. Stop.
他看不見你
He can't see you.
他們都一樣
None of them can.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
我要怎么讓他們停止
How can I make them stop?
你沒辦法 你的力量被音調壓過了
You can't. Your powers are being overridden by the tower.
我們走
I got you.
我們走 這里
Let's go. This way.
這里 快來
This way. Come on.
快來 快來
Come on, come on.
住手‥
Stop! Stop!
住手
Stop it!
－這是因為我做的事嗎  －太遲了
- Is this because of what I did? - It's too late.
是因為我在奧林匹亞做的事嗎
Is this because of what I did at Olympiad?
這不是你做的
You didn't do this.
我們得離開這里
We got to get out of here.
不要 我要解答
No. I want answers.
為什么這些人看不見我
Why can't these people see me?
因為你不在這個世界
Because you're not in this world.
世界是真的 但你不是
It's real, but you're not.
待續
雙語合并：James丶xz
謝謝觀賞